ACTWU Labor Unity Photograph Files 5981 P
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
ACTWU Labor Unity Photograph Files
1912-1976
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
5981 P
23.5 cubic feet
23.5 linear ft.
Photographs.
This is a collection of over 12,000 photographs, covering over sixty years of history of the Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union.
5745657
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, December 19, 2013
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, April 18, 2019
Biographical / Historical
The Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America, the most significant union representing workers in the men's clothing industry, was founded in New York City in 1914 as a breakaway movement from the United Garment Workers. Radical and immigrant workers in the tailors' and cutters' locals were the core of the seceding group, which advocated industrial unionism and economic strikes in opposition to the UGW's craft organization, which they saw as conservative and timid. Their diverging views had come to the fore during the historic 1910 dispute at the Chicago firm Hart, Schaffner, and Marx. The opposition called the strike against the UGW leadership's advice, and reached a path-breaking agreement with management that established an arbitration system to settle disputes.
Members flocked to the new union. Around 50,000 strong at its founding, by 1920 the ACWA counted about 170,000 members. Initially composed mostly of immigrants of Jewish European descent with Socialist leanings, the ACWA quickly welcomed members of a great number of nationalities and diverse backgrounds. Like in other garment unions, most workers and many members were women, but the leadership was predominantly male, a situation that did not change for many decades. Early on the union adopted a centralized administrative structure combined with industrial unionism, with the joint boards' by-laws having precedence over those of locals.
Espousing a philosophy perhaps brought over by its early immigrant socialist members, the Amalgamated went beyond bread and butter issues and adopted a distinctive form of social unionism that was largely absent in the American labor movement. Starting in the 1920s, it provided educational opportunities and recreational facilities for its members, as well as services such as an insurance plan, banks offering personal loans at low interest rates, low-cost housing cooperatives, medical clinics, and even union- owned restaurants.
Sidney Hillman was the first president of the new union and the most important officer in its history. He applied his experience as bargaining representative in Chicago to the whole industry. Under his leadership the union made significant strides in securing better wages and working conditions for its members, and at the same time it consolidated gains and provided stability to the industry through the widespread adoption of the arbitration system tested at Hart, Schaffner, and Marx. Hillman paid close attention to industry issues, such as production, pricing, and marketing. In order to help management meet the competition of non-union firms, the union conducted studies of efficiency, work methods, and factory costs. Letters to the official publication of the union, Advance, document the controversy that ensued within the union over what was perceived to be collaboration with management.
Hillman also understood the importance of labor's involvement in national affairs and political action. In the 1920s the ACWA sent delegates to the Conference for Progressive Political Action and to the Farmer-labor party conventions. Although many members and officers were Socialists, the union stopped short of officially endorsing the party. Communist attempts at gaining influence within the union were firmly curbed. Hillman's participation in national affairs and politics became prominent during the New Deal, when he became a close advisor to Franklin D. Roosevelt on labor and economic issues. He also served on the board of the National Recovery Administration. Later, during World War II, he helped establish the Labor's Non Partisan League. He was also named associate director of the Office of Production Management, which assisted in mobilizing the nation's resources for the war effort. Hillman's prestige perhaps reflected the healthy condition of his union, which by the end of the conflict was strong and stable.
During the post World War II period the union faced a number of significant challenges. Membership continued to grow (peaking at 395,000 in 1968), but the union's political influence and visibility in national affairs declined. In their never ending pursuit of lower production costs, many firms relocated to the South, forcing the union to engage in large organizing efforts. Simultaneously, signs began to appear of changes that would lead to the almost complete demise of the domestic apparel industry and, ultimately, to the erosion of union membership. Foreign imports of cheap clothing goods steadily grew in the 1950s and 1960s, and mushroomed in the following two decades, plunging employment in the apparel sector into a steady decline. Union efforts to stem the tide included Buy American campaigns and extensive lobbying in Congress, but they were to no avail. In 1976, the ACWA merged with the Textile Workers of America to become the Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union. Despite successful and much publicized nationwide actions such as the Farah boycott and the J.P. Stevens corporate campaign, the woes threatening the union's existence continued unabated. The fate of the domestic industry was sealed in the late 1970s and the 1980s by the flight of firms chasing tax breaks and cheap labor abroad. By 1995, when ACTWU voted to merge with the International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union, their combined membership was 350,000. The new Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees (UNITE!) seemed poised to infuse new life in a troubled union.
Scope and Contents
This is a collection of over 12,000 photographs, covering over sixty years of history of the Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5619 P: ACTWU Photographs
Arrangement
Series I: LABOR UNITY
Series II: OVERSIZE/HAT WORKER
Series III: JP STEVENS
Series IV: LEAFLETING
Series V: MISCELLANEOUS OVERSIZED
Clothing trade; Clothing workers -- Labor unions; Textile industry; Textile workers -- Labor unions; Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union
5745657
- Series I: LABOR UNITY
  - Aaron, Hank., 1974 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Scope and Contents
    Includes: Hank Aaron's 715th Home Run, Atlanta Stadium -- April 8, 1974.
  - Abel, I.W., 1976 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Includes: Addressing ACTWU Convention 1976; President Finley and President Abel laughing; Men talking; group shot; Sheinkman giving speech at Washington dinner; President Abel keynoting at conference; meeting Executive Committee of AFL - CIO.
  - Aberdeen., 1994 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Includes: NY Joint Board on strike against Aberdeen Jan. - Feb. 1994; strikers.
  - Aberdeen Manufacturing Co. Mississippi., 1985 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Includes: Negotiating Committee, Jackson, Paine, Blanchard, Wilson, Randle, Bell, Forsyth Feb 1985; James Jackson reading contract to Aberdeen Manufacturing Co., employees before ratification; audience shots.
  - Abzug, Bella. (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Includes: Portrait; many proof/ contact sheets of speech, audience; various group shots.
  - Accardi, Connie. (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Includes: Close-up of Connie Accardi.
  - Adkins, Nettie. (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Includes: Nettie Adkins, retired Eastern Shore Joint Board Manager, surrounded by flowers, card, tea set.
  - AFL-CIO., 1975-1988 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Includes: Meeting; Labor News Conference; woman speaking; cartoons: unemployed, no-fault plan; AFL- CIO executive council meeting; AFL-CIO Convention Los Angeles, California; Convention 12/77 shots: speakers, audience, men conversing, many proof/co
  - AFL-CIO Convention, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 8a)
  - AFL-CIO Convention, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 8b)
  - AFL-CIO Convention. Hollywood, Florida., 1983 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Includes: ACTWU Secretary-Treasurer Jack Sheinkman speaking at AFL-CIO Convention; Finley AFL-CIO Convention; Lane Kirkland & Thomas Donahue AFL-CIO Convention; ACTWU delegates at AFL-CIO Convention; Walter Mondale at AFL-CIO Convention in Florida
  - AFL-CIO Convention, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Includes: AFL-CIO Convention, Sheinkman/Peter Sinoroda (?), Sam Nocella, talking; speaker at 1981 Convention; men talking; woman shaking hands; male speaker; Ted Kennedy speaking; male speaker; men at podium; close-up of male speaker; audience
  - AFL-CIO Convention, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Includes: Miscellaneous contact sheets. November, 1979
  - AFL-CIO Occupational Safety & Health Conference, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    Includes: Cavanaugh (Mike), Stevens (Amanda), Mullen (Donn), in Nashville, TN; Lewis Pressley, Jr., Ray Mullins and Cecil Jones; Kenneth Ferguson, Karen Sue Beck, Harry Groom; Chas. Sallee. December, 1987.
  - Aiello, Nick., 1985 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    Includes: Nick Aiello trip to U.S.S.R. 1985.
  - All State Lawn Products. (Box 1, Folder 14)
    Includes: Tony Herman, Harold B. Berg, Stan Artowicz, Mary Ann Zurek, Lorraine Berry, Chuck Carlson, Lucille Dahle, Anita Knutson, Ed Reynolds signing contract.
  - Amato Linen Supply. (Box 1, Folder 15)
    Includes: Woman with fliers; three women with pamphlets; contact sheet.
  - Amdur, Max (Manager, Cleveland Joint Board). (Box 1, Folder 16)
    Includes: Max Amdur, manager of hotel Wm Hill, and Marsh; meeting called by Ohio Public Interest Campaign: Nick Kostandaras, Toni Podojil, Bill Casstevens, Max Amdur (speaker), Joan Campbell, and Mark Real.
  - American Arbitration Association., 1977 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    Includes: 4/19/77 Lloyd McBride, William Winpisinger, Sol Chaikin, Jacob Sheinkman; contact sheets.
  - American Olean. (Box 1, Folder 18)
    Includes: Several contact sheets.
  - American Red Cross. (Box 1, Folder 19)
    Includes: ACTWU and American Red Cross agreement: Lewellys F. Barker, M.D., Walter G. Davis, Joyce Miller.
  - American Thread. (Box 1, Folder 20)
    Includes: Negotiating committee at American Thread Plant in Rosman, N.C.: Tom Kitchen, Alfred Morgan, Ellen Aryes, R.L. Roper, Helen McCall, Mary B. Orr.
  - Anastasoff, Alex. (Box 1, Folder 21)
    Includes: Portrait of Alex Anastasoff.
  - Anthony, Susan B. (coin). (Box 1, Folder 22)
    Includes: Front and back of coin.
  - Ashbrook, John (R-Ohio). (Box 1, Folder 23)
    Includes: Congressman John Ashbrook reading from documents prepared by J.P. Stevens in questioning union witnesses, Roanoke Rapids Congressional Hearing
  - Atkinson, Charles. (Box 1, Folder 24)
    Includes: Charles Atkinson speaks at Legislative Conference in Brunswick, Maine sponsored by three Health-Tex locals.
  - Australian Unionist. (Box 1, Folder 25)
    With contacts.
  - Automation., 1961 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    Includes: Machine girl serves hamburger to girl, 10/19/61.
  - Azzinaro, Samuel J. (Box 1, Folder 27)
    Includes: close-ups; giving speech; sitting with woman.
  - Baby Food. (Box 1, Folder 28)
    Includes: contact sheets; baby eating homemade baby food.
  - Bahamas., 1989 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    Includes: trade unionists at tables 5 and 15; man giving speech; men hugging; blowing out candles on cake with "25"; Service and Allied Industries Joint Board 9/89 at table with Bahamian trade unionists.
  - Bailey, Louise., 1980 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    Includes: Montgomery Stevens worker Louise Bailey interview 11/80.
  - Baker, Senator. (Box 1, Folder 31)
    Includes: close-up of Baker.
  - Bakery Workers. (Box 1, Folder 32)
    Includes: Women working assembly line.
  - Ballet Fabrics, Inc. (Box 1, Folder 33)
    Includes: group shots at table; smoking and eating; contact sheet.
  - Ballin Co. (Marieville, Quebec). (Box 1, Folder 34)
    Includes: photo of new shop: Sylvain Roy, Julie Caron, Rachel Brisson, Madeleine Vincent, Louis Laporte, Andre' di Tempora, Claudette Leblanc, Lynda Sage, Jacqueline Fontaine, Nicky Cristofaro.
  - Barber, Betty. (Box 1, Folder 35)
    Includes: close-up of Betty Barber.
  - Barkan, Al., 1976-1981 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    Includes: Convention 1981, Al Barkan speaking; 1976 Convention, Barkan and Ruth Price; Barkan addressing TWUA's 19th biennial convention, Gen. President Stetin; Alexander Barkan retires; close-up of Al Barkan 6/81.
  - Barron, Sara., 1992 (Box 1, Folder 37)
    Includes: Sara Barron Berinsky age 92, Baltimore, MD, 7/92; contact sheets.
  - Barton, Oma. with Editha Morris. (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Bauer, Donald. (Box 1, Folder 39)
    Includes: Ohio Hearing on J.P. Stevens, Father Donald J. Bauer with "A Special Report: The Sun Belt".
  - Bayh, Birch (D-Indiana)., 1979 (Box 1, Folder 40)
    Includes: portrait-like close-up (damaged); IN Leg. Conference 6/79; shaking hands over table; laughing with older woman; giving a speech; Sen. Birch Bayh receiving $500 check from Marion E. Grace.
  - Beame, Abe. (Box 1, Folder 41)
    Includes: Group shots; portraits; shots of Beame posed with Proclamation.
  - Beatty Carpet. (Box 1, Folder 42)
    Includes: Beatty Carpet Little Falls, N.J. meeting; contact sheets.
  - Beck, Burt. (Box 1, Folder 43)
    Includes: speech (damaged); Beck speaking at GEB Meeting Bal Harbour, Florida.
  - Becker Jeans Corp. (Miss.). Empty. (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Belding Corticelli. (Box 1, Folder 45)
    Includes: snapshot of Mme Liliane Levert, Mme Gladys Drake, and Mme Anita Blanchette.
  - Bellamy, Carol., 1983 (Box 1, Folder 46)
    Includes: 1983 Carol Bellamy and Toppin, speaking at Louis and Irene Simon Scholarships; NYC Council President Carol Bellamy and Myrtle Cribbs.
  - Bellamy, Walt. (Box 1, Folder 47)
    Includes: playing basketball for the Hawks; endorsing J.P. Stevens boycott, pictured with ACTWU VP Oma Barton; Atlanta Hawks portraits.
  - Benensohn, Dr. Sol. (Box 1, Folder 48)
    Includes: Benensohn posed with citation from Grocery and Food Product Local 738 of the International Brotherhood of Teamsters.
  - Bentsen, Lloyd, Sen. (D-Tex), 1986 (Box 1, Folder 49)
    Includes: Bentsen speaking; Finley giving speech; Bentsen and Finley conversing; group shots; speaking into Channel 7 microphone; portrait: hand-shake.
  - Berven Rug Mills., 1977 (Box 1, Folder 50)
    Includes: Berven Rug Delegates at West Coast Regional Joint Board March 27, 1977: Ed West, Sol Stetin, David Holocuer, Mary Patlan, Frank Nicholas, and John Stall Smith; committee members from Berven Rug Mills, Fresno, C.A.: Landry, Navarrete, West Martin
  - Bessette, Andre. (Box 1, Folder 51)
    Includes: Portrait of Bessette; Mt. Royal, Montreal St. Joseph Oratory, building and tourists.
  - Big Oil Protest. (Box 1, Folder 52)
    Includes: contact sheets of Big Oil Protest Day; 44 members of ACTWU Local 671 in Salisbury, Mo. marching against Big Oil; 9000 people gathered at the Federal Building in Chicago.
  - Big Wells, Texas - Mayor. (Box 1, Folder 53)
    Includes: Alicia Oregel standing by City Hall sign; Oregel at desk; Oregel smoking; Oregel in office; close-ups of Oregel; contact sheet.
  - Bingham, Eula. (Box 1, Folder 54)
    Includes: OSHA Director Eula Bingham speaking at meeting; portrait, contact sheet.
  - Birdair Dome. (Box 1, Folder 55)
    Includes: man and woman with buttons; audience shots; Richard A. Slisz, Business Agent and Betty LaCopa, President Local 1906.
  - Biscardi, Al. (Box 1, Folder 56)
    Includes: copies of Al Biscardi, New York business agent, giving a check to Paul O'Dwyer, candidate for New York City Council President, from the New York Joint Board Political Action Committee.
  - Black Monday In Youngstown (story). (Box 1, Folder 57)
    Includes: attorney Staughton Lynd, unemployed steelworkers John McNichol and Len Balluck, and attorney Bob Slyde; Frank and Angeline Nolfi; Youngstown Steel Shutdowns; view of the Campbell Works of Youngstown Sheet and Tube; Ellen Robinson and Marsha
  - Black Trade Unionist., 1977 (Box 1, Folder 58)
    Includes: Murray Finley receiving plaque; Finley, Annie Martin, and Walter Davis with plaques; Black Trade Unionists awards 1977; Secretary of Labor Peter J. Brennan receiving the Second Annual Award of Merit from the Black Trade Unionist Committee, N
  - Black Youth Unemployment. (Box 1, Folder 59)
    Includes: close-ups of Robert Ford Jr., Diane Lawrence, Benvende Walker, Alonzo Johnson, Michael Bethea; contact sheets.
  - Blackwell, Danny., 1979 (Box 1, Folder 60)
    Includes: Danny Blackwell speaking at Stevens Stockholders meeting, March 1979.
  - Blair, Ed., 1956 (Box 1, Folder 61)
    Includes: 6/25/56 Ed Blair with Jim Carey after Blair shot.
  - Blais, Denis Adrien. (Box 1, Folder 62)
    Includes: Portrait of Blais; Blais keynoting the Northern Wage Conference, pictured with Richard MacFadyen, Scott Hoyman, William DuChessi, Sol Stetin, Paul Swaity, and Thomas Pitarys.
  - Bleyer Industries (Mount Union, PA). (Box 1, Folder 63)
    Includes: Snapshots of Bleyer Industries Neg. Comm.: Tom Swope, Brenda Morrow, Judy Christoff, and Sheila Alesi.
  - Blood Drive NYC. (Box 1, Folder 64)
    Includes: woman having blood drawn; many donors on beds; shots of female workers; contact sheets; Blood Drive.
  - Blue Moon Odom. (Box 1, Folder 65)
    Includes: two men looking at machinery.
  - Book Reviews., 1920-1929 (Box 1, Folder 66)
    Includes: cover of Archie Robinson's biography: George Meany and his Times; author Georgakas with 110-year-old Vanacha Temur, oldest authenticated citizen in Soviet Georgia, toasting; dock workers, Mobile, Alabama, 1920's; audience clapping.
  - Bookshelves., 1981 (Box 1, Folder 67)
    Includes: Mrs. Joan Suarez donating books on behalf of the Amalgamated Clothing and Textiles Workers Union, Dr. Truett L. Chance, George Ozuna Jr., and J.O. Wallace, Dec. 1981; "Labor Bookshelves"; contact sheet for bookshelf; Steve Turner's Night Shi
  - Bouhuys, Arend., 1979 (Box 1, Folder 68)
    Includes: Dr. Arend Bouhuys outside the mobile medical unit in Columbia, SC in April 1979, with Shorty Gamble, Essie Briggs, and Gertrude Brown.
  - Bowyer, Dick (Reverend). (Box 1, Folder 69)
    Includes: the Reverend Dick Bowyer speaking with Sam Hirsch of New York.
  - Boy Scouts. (Box 1, Folder 70)
    Includes: Mauro De Fazio presents the George Meany Award Medal to Local 119A member Albert Joseph Jr., Kathy Joseph; Miller and four Scouts.
  - Boys Town of Italy. (Box 1, Folder 71)
    Includes: presentation of $33,000 check to Monsignor John Patrick Carroll Abbing by ACTWU Vice Presidents Vincent Ricciardelli and Murray Goldstein; inauguration of August Bellanca Memorial Library: Carroll-Abbing, Goldstein, Caleca, Secretario, Sheink
  - Sen. Bill Bradley 10/84., 1984 (Box 1, Folder 72)
    Includes: Bradley speaks at ACTWU meeting of supporters in Clifton, NJ; Bill Bradley meeting with NJ leader 10/16/84; contact sheet.
  - Bradley, Tom., 1973 (Box 1, Folder 73)
    Includes: Tom Bradley visiting ACWA Shop at Labaron Clothing with Tony Fama, Robert Aubry, and Harry Bloch; August 1973 Los Angeles Mayor Thomas Bradley shaking hands.
  - Brand-Rex Division of Akzona Willimantic, Conn., 1977 (Box 1, Folder 74)
    Includes: joint union-company fund raising committee in 1977: W. Emack, E. St. Marie, L. Desrosiers, J. Adams, P. Shine, C. Lakes and A. Penardo.
  - Brandwen, Maxwell., 1976 (Box 1, Folder 75)
    Includes: Maxwell in office; contact sheets; in meeting as President of Amalgamated Bank, 1976; speech.
  - Brandzel, Sol. (Box 1, Folder 76)
    Includes: Brandzel in crowd; looking at paper; Brandzel honored by Histadrut: Harry Kirshenbaum, Murray Finley, Brandzel, Julius Ginsberg, Bayard Rustin, and Mrs. Ruth Brandzel; group shots; award presented to Sol Benensohn by Sol Brandzel; contact
  - Brantford-Canada. (Box 1, Folder 77)
    Includes: contact sheets.
  - Bread and Roses. (Box 1, Folder 78)
    Includes: cover art: woman with afro, flowers.
  - Brice, William. (Box 1, Folder 79)
    Includes: contact sheets, negatives; Brice and Wayne Brice, his son, in Wallace, NC grocery store.
  - British Textile Workers. (Box 1, Folder 80)
    Includes: contact sheet.
  - British Trade Unionists. (Box 1, Folder 81)
    Includes: British unionist D. Lambert with ACTWU officers Stetin, Finley, Sheinkman, and Hoyman; meeting: Sol Stetin, Pete Booth, Dr. Ronald Owen, Fred Dyson, Harry McGroaty, George Perkel, and Murray H. Finley.
  - Broadbent, Ed (Federal NDP Leader). (Box 1, Folder 82)
    Includes: portrait of Broadbent; Broadbent speaking at meeting; Broadbent interview; Ed Broadbent walks the picket line with 90 members of UAW Local 1620; Ed Broadbent and CLC president Dennis McDermott shake hands.
  - Brooks, John. (Box 1, Folder 83)
    Includes: portrait for campaign.
  - Broom, Sarah. (Box 1, Folder 84)
    Includes: portrait of Sarah Broom; Sarah Broom in front of "Norma Rae" poster.
  - Brown, Gerald. (Box 1, Folder 85)
    Includes: Gerald Brown elected to Georgia Democratic Committee.
  - Brown, Jerry (Gov. Calif.)., 1977 (Box 1, Folder 86)
    Includes: 12/77 speeches to AFL-CIO, ACTWU, etc.
  - Brown University. (Box 1, Folder 87)
    Includes: Contact sheets; people at table; meeting at church; meeting in classroom; Hillary Horne, Paul Cromwell, and Peter Goldberg of Brown University visited Stevens plants in the south.
  - Bryn Mawr Summer School Story. (Box 1, Folder 88)
    Includes: older woman reading letter (Louise Branthwaite); Helen Chamberlain reminisces.
  - Bucks County Housing. (Box 15, Folder 1)
    Includes: contact sheet; Carmen Watts and Penny Charleston standing outside house, Langhorne, PA.
  - Budget Ax Hits Workers (story)., 1981 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    Includes: contact sheets; Margaret Clark, TAA recipient, April 1981; Margaret Clark, Virginia Faye Bates and Margaret Jones at kitchen table; Margaret Clark stacking logs.
  - Buffalo Workshop (jobless). (Box 15, Folder 3)
    Includes: Sarah Mae Jackson, Buffalo Joint Board member; Michael Retzer, Buffalo Jt. Bd. Pres.; Larry Zgoda, treasurer Local 49.
  - Bumpers, Dale L. (Senator-Ark). (Box 15, Folder 4)
    Includes: contact sheet of SWRUB and Bumpers meeting; 4th Canadian Conference, group of delegates studying their resolutions.
  - Bunche, Ralph. (Box 15, Folder 5)
    Includes: Professor V.S. Emelyanov of the USSR meets Sterling Cole, with Dr. Ralph Bunche.
  - Bush, Clyde. (Box 15, Folder 6)
    -- Collection re-housed - formerly - box 1, ff 94 -- Includes: Clyde Bush and James Johnson.
  - Bush, George. (Box 15, Folder 7)
    -- Collection re-housed - formerly - box 1, ff 95 -- Includes: Hong Kong shirt shop with picture of George Bush in window; George Bush with Hong Kong shirt makers.
  - Bykofsky, Sidney., 1983 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    -- Collection re-housed - formerly - box 1, ff 96 -- Includes: contact sheets; Bykofsky receiving ACTWU award; Syd Bykofsky installed president of the National Yiddish Theatre; Bykofsky Retirement dinner, presented with plaque by Kilmer Caban and Jack She
  - Byrd, Robert C. (D-W. Va)., 1977 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    -- Collection re-housed - formerly - box 1, ff 97 -- Includes: head shots; 1977 portrait.
  - Caban, Kilmer. (Box 15, Folder 10)